myproperty.com.au 2018-03-16

# Tenant Management Made Easy For Landlords - MyProperty

## MYPROPERTY PRIVACY POLICY

Flexiproperty Pty Ltd ACN 142 088 855 t/as MyProperty is committed to protecting your privacy. 

MyProperty will only collect, use, disclose and store any personal information in accordance with the Australian National Privacy Principles set out in the Privacy Act 1988 (the “Act”), all Australian and U.S. privacy legislation, and this privacy policy. 

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for the (http://myproperty.com) website. 

This privacy policy (together with the MyProperty terms and conditions sets out the basis on which any personal information we collect from you, or¬¬ that you provide to us, will be processed by us. 

By agreeing to use MyProperty’s services you agree that you consent to MyProperty using your personal information together with any sensitive personal information, as set out in this document and in our terms of service. 

What Information We Collect

The types of information that MyProperty collects fall under two general categories: personally identifiable information (PII) and non-personally identifiable information (non-PII), including, where relevant, sensitive information as defined in the Act. 

PII consists of any information which can be used to specifically identify you as an individual, whereas non-PII consists of aggregate information or any information that does not specifically identify you as an individual. The following sections describe how your PII and non-PII are collected by us, and how we use such information. 

How We Collect and Use Information

_Log Files._ Any time you visit our website, we may gather information from your browser (such as your IP addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks) to analyse trends, administer the site, prevent fraud, track visitor movement in the aggregate, and gather demographic information. For example, we may log your IP address for system administration purposes. IP addresses are logged to track a user’s session. This gives us an idea of which parts of our site users are visiting. 

_Cookies._ We use “cookies” to keep track of some types of information while you are visiting our website or using our services. Cookies also allow us to save user preferences and track user trends. 

_Web Beacons._ “Web beacons” (also known as “clear gifs” and “pixel tags”) are small transparent graphic images that are often used in conjunction with cookies in order to further personalize our website for our users and to collect a limited set of information about our visitors. We may use web beacons in email communications in order to understand the behaviour of our customers. 

_Information About You._ When you register or participate in our services, we collect a wide variety of information about you. We will use personal information that you submit to provide our services to you. We will also share collected information including your personal information with our business partners to provide our services to you. 

_E-mails, Telephone Calls and Short Message Service (SMS)._ MyProperty complies with the requirements of the Australian Spam Act 2003 (Cth). 

_Geo-targeting_ We may collect information about you through "geo-targeting" technology built into the MyProperty app(s) for mobile devices. 

We require an e-mail address from you when you register for our services. We use your e-mail for both transactional and promotional purposes. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the MyProperty and third party products and services. We may also contact you by telephone or text message. If you would rather not receive telephone calls or text messages from us, you may ask to be removed from our contact list if you receive a call or text message from us. 

Disclosure of Your Information to Third Parties

_To third party service providers._ We use third party services such as marketing, financial and property service providers to provide our service. We may share information you provide with these third parties in order to provide our service. 

_Disclosure By Law._ You acknowledge and agree that MyProperty may disclose information you provide if required or permitted to do so by law, or if we, in our sole discretion, believe that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law, requests or orders from law enforcement, or any legal process; (2) protect or defend My Property’s rights; or (3) protect another person’s from damage. 

_Information Transferred Overseas._ We process all information, including your PII, via our servers and networks located outside of Australia. We may also use cloud service or software as a service providers where information collected may be transferred outside of Australia. By using our services and expressly assenting to this privacy policy, you have consented to the overseas transfer of your PII for the purpose of providing you the services for which you have registered or to which you have subscribed. We take all reasonable steps to ensure that all overseas recipients will not hold, use or disclose your PII inconsistently with the National Privacy Principles. 

Third-Party Advertising

We may use third-party advertising agencies or other service providers to serve ads on our website on behalf of My Property or third-party advertisers (e.g., retailers of goods or services). These companies may employ cookies and beacons (also known as single pixel gifs or action tags) to measure advertising effectiveness. 

Links to Other Sites

MyProperty is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites that may be linked to this site or of any third party advertisers. 

Access to Collected Information

You may contact us at contact@myproperty.com to access and/ or revise information we have collected about you. 

Contacting the Website

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with the MyProperty website, you can contact us at contact@myproperty.com 

Acceptance of Privacy Policy

Your use of our website, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this privacy policy and the Terms and Conditions of Service

Effective Date

This privacy policy was last revised on 16 December 2014.
